The Christmas Shoes is a drama, tv movie film directed by Andy Wolk.
Two separate stories mesh - in the first, a young music teacher, Maggie Andrews, begins dying of a heart
condition and her son Nathan tries to get a pair of Christmas shoes for her before she dies.
In the second, lawyer Robert Layton and his wife Kate are slowly drifting apart and the matter
comes to a head during Christmas when Kate takes over for Maggie for the school choir.
Robert Layton, played by Rob Lowe.
Maggie Andrews, played by Kimberly Williams-Paisley.
Nathan Andrews, played by Max Morrow.
Kate Layton, played by Maria del Mar.
Jack Andrews, played by Hugh Thompson.
Dalton Gregory, played by Dorian Harewood.
The Christmas Shoes is a 2002 American-Canadian made-for-television drama film based on the song
and the novel of the same name which was broadcast on CBS on December 1, 2002.
It was shot in Halifax, Nova Scotia.
It is the first in a series of ten books by VanLiere and
the first movie made from the series.
There have been four additional movies made from the series, The Christmas Blessing (2005), The
Christmas Hope (2009), The Christmas Secret (2014) and The Christmas Note (2015).
The tone is emotional.